

Contact

- - 034 381 8315
- nguyen.ken.v@gmail.com



- Thủ Đức City, HCM City
- kietnguyen.xyz
- kietnguyen01
- in <u>kietvnguyen</u>

Skills

Analytics:

- Predictive Analytics
- Statistical Analysis
- Data Visualization
- Machine Learning
- Data Mining

Programming:

- JavaScript
- Pvthon
- SQL

Tools:

- Power BI
- Jupyter
- Tableau
- Airflow
- Excel
- JIRA

Interests

- Struggling on the guitar
- Having fun with A.I.
- Lifting weights

Kiet Nguyen (Ken)

Data Analyst

I am a data analytics graduate with a diverse work experience in supply chain, web design, and IT support. I have a strong understanding of data modeling, machine learning, and data visualizations. I am proficient in Python, SQL, Power BI, and various DBMS. I have applied my analytical skills to manage warehouse inventory and equipment for multiple Fortune 500 companies. I have also worked with many clients on website design and SEO analytics. I hold a master's degree in data analytics and a bachelor's degree in economics.

Experience

2021 - 2022

Fastenal I Capitol Heights, MD, USA **Supply Chain Associate**

- Handled industrial equipment needs for multiple Fortune 500 companies on a weekly basis.
- · Managed Personal Protective Equipment (PPE) inventory for three Amazon warehouses
- Oversaw deliveries and installations of industrial PPE machines for Nordstrom warehouses.
- · Assisted with the opening of a new Amazon warehouse in Hyattsville, MD by coordinating on-site equipment deliveries.
- · Maintained optimal inventory for clients during their peak and off-season to reduce their expenditures.

2018-2020

KWD | Hyattsville, MD, USA

Web Designer

- Ensured web applications responsiveness across multiple browsers and devices.
- Designed dynamic sites with features and functionalities according to clients' requirements, needs, and budget.
- Consulted with clients throughout the development life cycle to minimize defects and maintain the desired level of quality.
- Performed regular maintenance, security updates, and performance optimizations.
- Managed SEO analytics to improve traffic performance.

2018-2020

Run Your Race Ministries | Riverdale, MD, USA **IT Support Technician**

- Provided efficient and effective assistance to staff and other users with software and hardware issues.
- · Diagnosed and resolved a wide range of computer-related issues, including hardware and software problems, network connectivity issues, and security vulnerabilities.
- · Maintained accurate records of all support requests and resolutions, ensuring that all issues were tracked and documented for future reference.
- · Provided training and support to staff and other users on the use of various software applications, including Microsoft Office, email clients, and other productivity tools.

Education

O 2021 - 2023

Western Governors University

Master of Science in Data Analytics

- Exploratory Data Analysis
- Statistical Modeling
- Data Cleaning
- Machine Learning
- **Business Analysis**
- Data Scraping
- Database Design
- ETL Architecture
- Data Processing

O 2010-2014

University of Maryland

Bachelor of Arts in Economics